2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "Yesterday, I __________ to a concert that __________ three hours.";went/lasted;go/lasted;went/last;go/lasts
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "I __________ too much this afternoon. Now, I have a stomachache.";ate;eat;eating;eaten
2;Básico;Past simple;Fill in the gap with the correct alternative: "I__________ until 10 o'clock this morning, then I went to my friend's house.";slept;sleeped;sleep;sleeps
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct answer: "I __________ a new car a week ago.";bought;buying;buy;buyed
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the incorrect alternative: I called her __________, but she wasn't home.";tomorrow;this morning;yesterday;on Sunday
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: " _______________ last weekend?";Where were you;Where was you;Where you were;Where you was
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative:"__________ you __________ a good time at the beach last summer?";Did/have;Did/had;Do/had;Do/have
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "__________ you __________ your work yesterday?";Did/finish;Did/finished;Do/finished;Do/finish
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ you __________ to the party yesterday?";Did/go;Did/do;Do/went;Did/went
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "It is my friend's birthday today. I __________ her a present yesterday.";bought;brought;buy;buying
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "They _______________ to work last week. They were on holiday.";didn't go;didn't do;went;were
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "Thomas _______________ to work yesterday because he was ill.";didn't go;doesn't go;didn't do;wasn't
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "These are the photos that we __________ on our last trip.";took;taken;take;taking
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "He __________ his wife with flowers last night.";surprised;surprise;is surprised;surprising
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "Yesterday, I __________ to the supermarket after work.";went;go;did;make
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "I __________ some Christmas presents this morning.";bought;buy;buying;buys
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "I __________ my wallet at home.";forgot ;forget;forgetting;forgotten
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct answer: "Did you __________ your homework in the morning?";do;did;made;wrote
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "Two years ago, I __________ to the USA with my family.";traveled ;travels;travel;traveling
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct answer: "Peter __________ the TV and __________ to bed.";turned off/went;turn off/went;turn off/go;turned off/go
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the question: "__________ you __________ your trip to South Africa last month?";Did/enjoy;Did/enjoyed;Do/enjoyed;Do/enjoy
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct answer: "Last month, I __________ to Mexico to visit my friends.";went;travel;go;was
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "Thanks for yesterday. I really _________ the party.";enjoyed;enjoy;enjoying;enjoys
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "My boss _______________ the meeting this morning. So, I'm free.";canceled;cancel;canceling;didn't cancel
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "I was born in Canada, but I __________ up in the USA.";grew;grow;grown;growing
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "She __________ all day long after that long flight on Monday.";slept;sleeps;sleep;is sleeping
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the question: "__________ you __________ Tim at school yesterday?";Did/see;Did/saw;Do/saw;Do/see
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct answer: "Sarah __________ a new iPad last week.";bought;buys;is buying;buy
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "The teacher __________ angry because I _______________ my homework.";was/didn't do;was/didn't make;are/didn't do;were/didn't do
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "Grandma __________ me a nice present for my birthday last year.";gave;give;gives;buy
2;Básico;Past simple;|Complete the dialogue: 
Sarah: "__________ Pam finally __________ to Paris last year?"
Tom: "No, she didn't. She's still living here."|;Did/move;Was/move;Do/move;Is/moving
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the question: "Where __________ you __________  last Christmas?";did/spend;do/spend;are/spending;do/spent
2;Básico;Past simple;|Complete the dialogue:
Aimee: "Where __________ you last night?"
Paul: "I __________ at home."|;were/was;are/was;were/am;was/am not
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct answer: "Jimmy __________ a fantastic book last year.";wrote;write;writes;is writing
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "She __________ all her belongings and __________ to London last month.";sold/moved;sell/move;sells/moves;sells/moved
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "He __________ very tired, so he __________ late today.";was/woke up;was/wakes up;was/wake up;were/woke up
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct answer: "Sam __________ the bus one hour ago.";caught;catch;catches;is catching
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "Your phone __________ just a minute ago.";rang;ring;rings;is ringing
2;Básico;Past simple;|Complete the dialogue:
Sue: "Would you like some water?"
Karen: "No, thank you. I __________ some just a minute ago."|;drank;drink;drink;am drinking
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the question: "__________ Peter _________ in time for his interview yesterday?";Did/arrive;Was/arrive;Were/arrive;Does/arrive
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "She __________ jogging after class this morning.";went;go;gone;does
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct answer: "Mark and John _______________ her the truth in the past.";didn't tell;doesn't tell;is telling;tell
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "We _________ them at a party last week.";met;meet;meets;don't meet
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "I __________ my new dress to the party last night.";wore;wear;wears;am wearing
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the question: "I can't find my glasses anywhere! __________ you ___________ them?;Did/see;Were/seeing;Was/seeing;Does/see
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "They __________ breakfast and then __________ the kids to school this morning.";had/drove;had/drive;have/drove;has/drove
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "Last night you were so tired that you _______________ goodnight." ;didn't say;didn't tell;don't say;wasn't saying
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "Oh, sorry, nobody __________ me it __________ a surprise party.";told/was;tells/was;told/is;told/were
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "Yesterday, the weather report __________ it was going to rain today.";said;say;is saying;says
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "The bus was taking too long, so I __________ a cab to the airport.";took;take;have to take;am taking
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "I __________ a lot yesterday. __________ pizza, salad, chocolate cake and ice cream.";ate/had;ate/have;eat/have;ate/I'm having
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "I think I __________ you last week. __________ at the mall?";saw/Were you;saw/You were;seen/You were;see/Were you
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "My trip was great. I __________ some really nice people." ;met;meet;see;seen
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "When I __________ in France yesterday, I __________ straight to the Eiffel Tower.";arrived/went;arrive/am going;arrival/went;arrived/am going
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "My friends and I __________ to Barbados last vacation. It __________ a fantastic trip.";went/was;go/is;going/was;went/were
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "We __________ to our new house last summer.";moved;move;are moving;moves
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "I __________ the bus this morning because I __________ up late.";missed/woke;miss/wake;am missing/am waking;miss/woke
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "I remember the first time we __________. It __________ a very cold day.";met/was;meet/was;met/were;meet/is
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "What a coincidence! I _______________ Alice __________ your sister.";didn't know/was;didn't know/is;don't know/is;didn't know/were
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "I was nervous because the director __________ me to __________ in public.";asked/speak;asked/spoke;asks/speak;ask/speak
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "I __________ your parents on the street this morning. They __________ in a hurry.";saw/were;seen/were;see/are;seen/are
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "Your boss __________ me you are doing a very nice job, congratulations!";told;tells;is telling;tell
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "I _______________ you 3 days ago but you _______________.";called/didn't answer;called/don't answer;called/not answered;was calling/weren't answering
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "It was a nice day. The children __________ soccer and __________ kites all day long.";played/flew;play/fly;played/flown;plays/flies
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "We __________ the hotel where we __________ our last vacation.";enjoyed/spent;enjoyed/spend;enjoyed/spending;enjoy/spend
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "Jane __________ my car this morning to __________ her father to the airport.";borrowed/take;borrowed/took;borrows/take;borrowed/taking
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "I closed the windows when it __________ to rain.";began;begin;begun;is beginning
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "My daughter __________ a glass of milk before she __________ for school this morning.";had/left;has/leaves;is having/is leaving;has/left
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "I'm starving. I _______________ anything to eat this morning.";didn't have;hadn't;don't have;wasn't having
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "I __________ that you __________ in the hospital yesterday. Are you OK?";heard/were;heard/was;heard/are;hear/were
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "I __________ my husband downtown and we __________ home for dinner.";met/went;meet/go;met/gone;meet/are going
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "I __________ lost in the city center this morning, but a kind man __________ me.";got/helped;get/helped;get/helps;got/helps
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the question: "Did your friend _________ you to keep the news a secret?";ask;asked;asks;has asked
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "I didn't __________ this report. Sarah __________ it.";write/wrote;wrote/wrote;write/writes;written/wrote
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "Yesterday was a beautiful day, we __________ to the beach and __________ in the sea.";went/swam;went/swim;go/swim;going/swimming
2;Básico;Past simple;|Complete the dialogue:
Olivia: "Where did you buy this shirt?"
Cary: "I didn't _________ it, it __________ a birthday present."|;buy/was;bought/was;bought/were;buy/were
2;Básico;Past simple;|Complete the dialogue:
Mary: "Did you __________ your birthday party?"
Cassia: "Yes, I __________ it, thank you."|;like/loved;liked/loved;liked/love;like/love
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "She __________ up early this morning and __________ swimming.";got/went;gets/went;gets/go;got/go
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the question: "Where __________ he __________? I was looking for him.";did/go;did/went;do/went;does/go
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the question: "What kind of games did you _________ when you __________ a child?";like/were;liked/were;like/was;liked/be
2;Básico;Past simple;|Complete the dialogue: 
Sam: "Where __________ you born?"
Lukas: "I __________ born in Switzerland."|;were/was;was/were;were/were;are/am
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the question: "What __________ the weather like last weekend?";was;were;is;be
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "We __________ a meeting from 9 to 12 o'clock, then we __________ to an Italian restaurant.";had/went;have/went;have/going;had/were
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the question: "What __________ for Cary's birthday?";did you buy;you bought;do you buy;you buy
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "He didn't __________ your sister had two children.";know;knew;knows;knowing
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "I _______________ at work last week. I __________ on vacation.";wasn't/was;weren't/were;wasn't/were;didn't go/was
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the question: "__________ you at the club yesterday? I think I __________ you.";Were/saw;Was/saw;Did/saw;Were/seen
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "I __________ you mother on the street this morning, but she _______________ me.";saw/didn't see;see/didn't see;saw/doesn't see;seen/doesn't see
2;Básico;Past simple;|Complete the dialogue:
Ben: "What time _______________ ?"
Joshua: "An hour ago."|;did Anne arrive;does Anne arrive;Anne arrive;Anne arrives
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "My mother and my father __________ married in 1981.";got;get;gets;are getting
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "Cary and Bruce __________  a lot of money on their last vacation.";spent;spend;spends ;are spending
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "Last weekend, Pamela and Bryan __________ a train from Paris to Amsterdam.";caught;catch;catches;are catching
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "I __________ to call my aunt on her birthday last Tuesday.";forgot ;forget;am forgetting;can't forget
2;Básico;Past simple;|Complete the dialogue:
Claire: "Where did James __________ on his last vacation?"
Patrick: "He __________ to Tahiti."|;go/went;went/went;go/goes;went/goes
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "My grandmother __________ me this ring when I turned 30.";gave;given;gives;is giving
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "Our teacher ________________ to class yesterday because she was sick.";didn't come;came;comes;isn't coming
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "Marcos __________ his CV to a law firm last week, but they didn't __________ him back.";sent/write;sent/wrote;send/wrote;send/write
2;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "We __________ to study, but it __________ hard to concentrate with all that noise.";tried/was;are trying/was;try/was;tried/were
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "Last time I __________ you, you ___________ just a child.";saw/were;see/was;seen/were;saw/was
2;Básico;Past simple;Complete the question: "Where __________ you __________ this ring? It's beautiful!";did/buy;did/bought;do/buy;do/bought
